// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which element refers to the time and location where the story happens?",
    answer: "b. setting",
    options: [
      "a. plot",
      "b. setting",
      "c. conflict",
      "d. characterization"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The phrase, “Don’t judge the book by its cover,” is an example of",
    answer: "d. conflict",
    options: [
      "a. mood",
      "b. detting",
      "c. theme",
      "d. conflict"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What do you call the most important character in a story?",
    answer: "b. protagonist",
    options: [
      "a. foil",
      "b. protagonist",
      "c. antagonist",
      "d. deuteragonist"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which plot structure creates tone, presents characters and other important details to introduce the story?",
    answer: "c. exposition",
    options: [
      "a. setting",
      "b. theme",
      "c. exposition",
      "d. climax"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which element of a short story is known as the vantage point used to narrate the story?",
    answer: "d. point of view",
    options: [
      "a. setting",
      "b. theme",
      "c. exposition",
      "d. point of view"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What do you call the character who contends with the main character in a short story?",
    answer: "c. antagonist",
    options: [
      "a. investigator",
      "b. protagonist",
      "c. antagonist",
      "d. instigator"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which element of a short story shows the author’s attitude or feelings?",
    answer: "d. tone",
    options: [
      "a. plot",
      "b. theme",
      "c. exposition",
      "d. tone"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What do you call the events that happen in a short story?",
    answer: "c. plot",
    options: [
      "a. setting",
      "b. theme",
      "c. plot",
      "d. conflict"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is considered as the essence of fiction?",
    answer: "c. conflict",
    options: [
      "a. setting",
      "b. theme",
      "c. conflict",
      "d. climax"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which do you call the series of events when the conflicts grow more complicated, suspense builds, and more details are added?",
    answer: "a. rising action",
    options: [
      "a. rising action",
      "b. theme",
      "c. exposition",
      "d. falling action"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which element is always presented at the final part of the story?",
    answer: "a. resolution",
    options: [
      "a. resolution",
      "b. theme",
      "c. exposition",
      "d. climax"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which element is considered as the turning point in the story?",
    answer: "d. climax",
    options: [
      "a. setting",
      "b. theme",
      "c. exposition",
      "d. climax"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which element refers to the series of events and character actions that relate to the central conflict?",
    answer: "c. plot",
    options: [
      "a. setting",
      "b. theme",
      "c. plot",
      "d. conflict"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which is considered as the base or beginning of a story?",
    answer: "c. exposition",
    options: [
      "a. setting",
      "b. theme",
      "c. exposition",
      "d. climax"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What comes after the climax when things or events begin to work out?",
    answer: "d. falling action",
    options: [
      "a. rising action",
      "b. theme",
      "c. exposition",
      "d. falling action"
    ]
  },
];
